<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What&#39;s Cookin&#39;</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on What&#39;s Cookin&#39;</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Cookies</title>
      <link>/big-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/big-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Cookies again! Before you go off thinking I&amp;rsquo;m slamming down a dozen sticks of butter each week with all these cookie posts, rest assured, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of broccoli and fresh cans of corn that don&amp;rsquo;t make the cut for a post here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac and Cheese and Sausage</title>
      <link>/mac-and-cheese-and-sausage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mac-and-cheese-and-sausage/</guid>
      <description>Every child dreams of waking up on Christmas morning to a nice hearty bowl of mac and cheese. Unfortunately, a garden-variety boxed mac and cheese doesn&amp;rsquo;t have anywhere near the protein levels that a growing boy or girl needs, so it&amp;rsquo;s time to improvise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bag of Potatoes</title>
      <link>/bag-of-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bag-of-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Potatoes have found their way into every facet of modern life. 100 years ago, a typical person would have seen a potato only a handful of times in their whole life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Showdown</title>
      <link>/cookie-showdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cookie-showdown/</guid>
      <description>Two eternal rivals finally put face to face in a head-on contest of flavor, texture, and cookedness. Who will win the Christmas cookie showdown? On one side of the ring is half of a Chili&amp;rsquo;s Skillet Cookie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupcookies</title>
      <link>/cupcookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cupcookies/</guid>
      <description>The cookie is a veritable swiss army knife of desserts. Though it provides some playful constraints, these conspire to create a platform that inspires creativity. You will often see cookies formed into a playful and exuberant shape, such as a dinosaur or a christmas tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled Cheeseburger</title>
      <link>/grilled-cheeseburger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/grilled-cheeseburger/</guid>
      <description>Coming in hot off the press, it&amp;rsquo;s a fresh take on the tired old grilled cheese. Before you say it&amp;rsquo;s just a patty melt, take a closer look!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Pea Smoothie</title>
      <link>/tea-pea-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tea-pea-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>No, not toilet paper! While similar in that you may have a tough time finding peas at the market this time of year, the tea pea smoothie is far more satisfying!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Bagels</title>
      <link>/pizza-bagels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pizza-bagels/</guid>
      <description>Everybody and their mother is talking about Bagel Bites these days. I&amp;rsquo;m tired of it! Bagel Bites are overdone, overpriced, and they always underdeliver. Things like that have no place in a home pantry, let alone a grocery store aisle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Peas</title>
      <link>/everything-peas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/everything-peas/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not everyday you get to go outside your comfort zone and experience what the world has to offer. I was lucky enough recently to find such a situation inside the confines of my own home, with these peas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Wheat Bread</title>
      <link>/bread-loaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bread-loaf/</guid>
      <description>Recently I had the pleasure (or displeasure, depending on who you ask) of being chosen to select a loaf of bread from my local grocer, Target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bowl o&#39; Brisket</title>
      <link>/beef-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beef-bowl/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s some disease going around these days; it has a variety of symptoms but the most prominent is an itch. An itch for Korean BBQ! But that can be tough to scratch to satisfaction in your own home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggs, Bacon, and Donuts</title>
      <link>/eggs-bacon-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/eggs-bacon-donuts/</guid>
      <description>If there was ever a time to play it safe with a meal, it&amp;rsquo;s breakfast time. Upon waking up, the human stomach needs several hours to kick into high gear before it can handle complex foods such as hamburgers, celery, and pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chips and Dips</title>
      <link>/chips-and-dips/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chips-and-dips/</guid>
      <description>In front of you a bountiful cornucopia overflows with tortilla chips. These chips are so bare and dry, they are practically begging for a dip to quench their thirst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broccoli Beef</title>
      <link>/broccoli-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/broccoli-beef/</guid>
      <description>Another copy-cat dish, broccoli beef hails from the hallowed halls of Panda Express. These days, recreating a fast food dish at home is hardly noteworthy, so there are a few twists and turns waiting to surprise us as we dig into this mound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Snack Platter</title>
      <link>/three-snack-plate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/three-snack-plate/</guid>
      <description>Not every meal can be the next Sistine Chapel ceiling of meals. Especially now with global temperatures on the rise and political discord in the streets, it&amp;rsquo;s important to find simplicity where you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Chessmen&#34;</title>
      <link>/chessmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chessmen/</guid>
      <description>The Pepperidge Farm Chessmen Butter Cookies have a rich buttery taste wrapped up in a soft, yet crackery, package. The cookies each have a single chessman (which includes the queen, mind you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leftover Potatoes Medley</title>
      <link>/leftover-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leftover-fries/</guid>
      <description>There comes a time in every man, woman, and child&amp;rsquo;s life when they must make a tough decision. Especially in these trying times, you will commonly find french fries, tater tots, potato wedges, and even fritters in your own home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pea Smoothie</title>
      <link>/pea-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pea-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>Frozen peas can work wonders for your health, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to vomit if I have to eat another bowl of steamed peas! Alas, there is another solution: that&amp;rsquo;s right, put them in a smoothie!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jjajangmyeon</title>
      <link>/jjajangmyeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jjajangmyeon/</guid>
      <description>Things are really starting to get cooking over here at whatscookin.biz! Today we have an exciting guest post from one of the foremost chefs in the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montaña de los Nachos</title>
      <link>/nachos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nachos/</guid>
      <description>The fabled &amp;ldquo;Montaña de los Nachos,&amp;rdquo; or, as you may know it, the &amp;ldquo;Nacho Mountain,&amp;rdquo; is a common delicacy enjoyed throughout the Americas. The ingredients vary, but pictured above is a basic, unoffensive mountain consisting of beans, cheese, shredded chicken, and strip-shaped tortilla chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Bean Salad</title>
      <link>/three-bean-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/three-bean-salad/</guid>
      <description>The obvious question that comes to mind is: &amp;ldquo;What are the three beans?&amp;rdquo; Like most things in life, there is a short answer and a long answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything But The Bagel Seasoning Plus Bagels</title>
      <link>/bagels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bagels/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while but I&amp;rsquo;m back, and with a bang. I&amp;rsquo;ve previously written on some alternative uses for Trader Joe&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Everything but the Bagel Sesame Seasoning Blend,&amp;rdquo; but here today we have a more traditional application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salmon Nuggets</title>
      <link>/salmon-nuggets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/salmon-nuggets/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Nugget&amp;rdquo; descends from the mid 1800s word &amp;ldquo;nug,&amp;rdquo; which means lump. Gold, chicken, and even turkey have been shaped into nugget form, but until recent times, the general public has not accepted fish-based nuggets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spicy Tajín Beans</title>
      <link>/spicy-tajin-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spicy-tajin-beans/</guid>
      <description>Countless people through the ages have scoured the world searching for the spice of life, but little did they know it could be found as nearby as their own kitchen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Pepper</title>
      <link>/black-pepper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/black-pepper/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d have a tough time finding a kitchen these days without black pepper hiding away in the spice cabinet. Everyone has no trouble flinging salt and pepper every which way on every piece of food that passes over their countertops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffin&#39;</title>
      <link>/stuffing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stuffing/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you read that right, we&amp;rsquo;re talking about stuffing. I know it&amp;rsquo;s far from Thanksgiving, but sometimes in life you have to say: to heck with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Bacon Lettuce Tomato Avocado Wraps</title>
      <link>/turkey-wraps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/turkey-wraps/</guid>
      <description>When I do see a clock that shows it&#39;s noon, my stomach growls with zeal of a baboon. I hurry t&#39;ward the kitchen pantry quick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Beans</title>
      <link>/everything-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/everything-beans/</guid>
      <description>This is a little concoction of mine I discovered not long ago. Combine a microwaved can of black beans (specifically S&amp;amp;W Organic Black Beans in an 8 pack from Costco) with some Trader Joe&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Everything but the Bagel Sesame Seasoning Blend&amp;rdquo; and you get something heretofore unheard of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Udon from a Bowl</title>
      <link>/udon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/udon/</guid>
      <description>It can be tough these days to find a good Japanese soup restaurant. But fortunately, food science has progressed to the point where Japanese soups and noodle dishes can be made right in your own kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bean Chili</title>
      <link>/bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Those who know me well know that I am a sucker for a nice pot of chili, for too many reasons to list out here. For just the highlights: it&amp;rsquo;s quick and it&amp;rsquo;s good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Gatorade</title>
      <link>/gatorade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gatorade/</guid>
      <description>These days Gatorade comes in all shapes, colors, and sizes. I typically stick with the traditional &amp;ldquo;Thirst Quencher&amp;rdquo; line of products, which comes in dozens of flavors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organic Honey Crunch n&#39; Oats Cereal</title>
      <link>/tj-cereal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tj-cereal/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s breakfast time! And unfortunately there are no Froot Loops to be found, so we will have to settle for Trader Joe&amp;rsquo;s Organic Honey Crunch n&amp;rsquo; Oats Cereal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mint Cookies and Cream Ice Cream</title>
      <link>/mint-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mint-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>To kick things off here on whatscookin.biz, I will doing a short review of the Mint Cookies and Cream ice cream from Archer Farms. It may surprise you to find out that Archer Farms is actually the predecessor of Target&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Good &amp;amp; Gather&amp;rdquo; store brand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>